Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Irish Americana Collection AIA.031.004
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Sheet Music (Irish), 1817-1995, 191937
  - O, 334239
    - On the Banks of Killarney, 1913-1915; 192324 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - On the Green Shores of Erin, 1923; 192323 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - On the Hoko Moko Isle, 1916; 192322 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - On the Road to Dublin Town, 1915; 192321 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - On Union Square, 1886; 192320 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Once Upon A Time, 1917; 192319 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - O'O'O'Brien, 1902; 192318 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Open the Door, dear Arrah, for me, 1865; 192317 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - O'Rafferty's Hare, 1949; 192316 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - O'Reagans, The, 1886; 192315 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - O'Reilly, 1904; 192314 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Ould Plaid Shawl, The, 1908; 192313 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Ould Plaid Shawl, The (2), 1895; 192312 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Over in Erin, 1917; 192311 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Over the Hills to Mary, 1915; 192310 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Over There, 1917; 192309 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - O Would I Were in Ireland, 1912; 192308 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - P, 334237
    - Paddy, 1906, 1933; 192307 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Paddy Carey, undated; 192306 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Paddy Carey's Fortune, undated; 192305 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Paddy Duffy's Cart, 1881; 192304 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Paddy McGinty's Goat, 1917; 192303 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Paddy O'Carroll, undated; 192302 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Paddy Shay, 1889; 192301 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Paddy's Day, 1905; 192300 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Paddy's Jig, 1955; 192299 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Paddy-the-next-best-thing, 1923; 192298 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Paddy Whack, 1907; 192297 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Pat Malloy, 1865; 192296 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Pat Malloy (2), 1867; 192295 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Patricia O'Brien, 1910; 192294 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Patsey McKim McCann, 1895; 192293 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Patsy, 1906, 1907; 192292 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Patsy Dear, 1907; 192291 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Pearl O'Rielly, 1936; 192290 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Peek-A-Boo, undated; 192289 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Peek-A-Boo (2), 1881; 192288 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Peggy, 1919; 192287 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Peggy (2), 1919; 192286 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Peggy Brady, 1903; 192285 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Peggy Cline, 1892; 192284 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Peggy Gilroy, 1913; 192283 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Peggy Malone, 1916; 192282 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Peggy McVey, 1918; 192281 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Peg O' My Heart, 1913, 1947; 192280 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Peggy O'Neal, 1903; 192279 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Peggy O'Neil, nd, 1921; 192278 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Pepita Maguire, 1904; 565208 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Phil the Fluter's Ball, 1938; 192277 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Pick A Little Four Leaf Clover, 1918; 192276 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Pictures in the Firelight, 1912; 192275 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Pinkerton Detective Moon, 1912; 192274 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Pipers of Kilkenny, The, 1937; 192273 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Plain Mamie O'Hooley, 1903; 192272 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Ploughman, The, 1951; 192271 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Policeman McGlue, 1887; 192270 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Poor Irish Boy, The, 1854; 192269 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Poor Mary Anne O'Shea, 1917; 192268 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Pretty Kitty Blue Eyes, 1944; 192267 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Pretty Kitty Doyle, 1896; 192266 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Pretty Kitty Kelly, 1920; 192265 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Pretty Mollie Shannon, 1901; 192264 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Pretty Molly Shannon, 1922; 192263 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Pride of Tipperary, The, 1925; 192262 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Primrose Waltz, 1896; 192261 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Princess of My Heart, The, 1917; 192260 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Prisoner's Song, The, 1924; 192259 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Pull the Cork out of Erin, 1917; 192258 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Purity, Honor, and Truth, 1894; 192257 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Put On Your Old High Hat, 1912; 192256 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - R, 334236
    - Rafferty, 1903; 192255 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Rafferty's Chime, 1914; 192254 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Rafferty's Racin' Mare, 1906; 192253 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Remember Boy You're Irish, 1888; 192252 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Remember the Poor, 1900; 192251 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Reminiscences of Ireland, undated; 192250 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Return With the Springtime Acushla Machree, 1915; 192249 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Rip Rip Rip, 1901; 192248 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Rising of the Moon, The, 1957; 192247 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - River Shannon Moon, 1923; 192246 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Rooney, 1958; 192245 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Rory O'Moore, undated; 192244 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Rory O'Mory and Me, 1948; 192243 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Rose Maguire, 1896; 192242 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Rose O'Day, 1941; 192241 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Rose of Kildare, The, 1912; 192240 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Rose of Killarney, 1876; 192239 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Rose of Tralee, 1933, 1935; 192238 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Rose of Washington Square, undated; 586656
    - Roses of Erin, The, 1911; 192237 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Rose Sweet Rose, 1904; 192236 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Rosie Machree, 1927; 192235 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Rosie O'Reilly, 1923; 192234 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Rosie O'Ryan, 1926; 192233 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Roving Kind, The, 1950; 192232 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - S, 334235
    - Sadie O'Brady, 1924; 192231 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Saint Patrick, undated; 192230 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Sally and Irene and Mary, 1921; 192229 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Santiago-Flynn, 1908; 192228 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Saturday Night in Dublin, 1950; 192227 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Savourneen Deelish, undated; 192226 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Savoy Irish Medley, The, 1924; 192225 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Say! Have You Seen O'Houlihan?, 1890; 192224 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Says I to Myself, Says I, 1917; 192223 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Scanlan's Rose Song, 1883; 192222 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - See Saw and Saw Saw, 1894; 192221 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Shadowland, 1914; 192220 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Shaeffer's Jig, undated; 192219 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Shaeffer's Jig (2), undated; 192218 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Shamrock and the Rose, The, 1915; 192217 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Shamrock Belles, 1912; 192216 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Shamus O'Brien, 1870; 192215 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Shannon, The Shamrocks, And You, The, 1951; 192214 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Shaughraun Quadrilles, The, 1877; 192213 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - She Lives in Donegal, 1941; 192212 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - She Lives on Munray Hill, 1882; 192211 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - She Never Kissed Anything Else Except the Blarney Stone, 1917; 192210 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Sheelah, 1907; 192209 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Sheelah Magee, 1894; 192208 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - She's A Flower from the Fields of Old Ireland, 1909; 192207 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - She's Another Sweet Mother Machree, 1927; 192206 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - She's the Daughter of Mother Machree, 1915; 192205 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - She's the Mother of Peggy O'Neal, 1921; 192204 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - She's Waiting in Old Ireland, 1913; 192203 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Sho-Heen Sho, 1955; 192202 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Shoogy-Shoo, The, 1897; 192201 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Silent, O'Moyle! Be the Roar of thy Water, 1961; 192200 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Silly Boy, The, 1883; 192199 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Since Arrah Wanna Married Barney Carney, 1907; 192198 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Since I Fell in Love with Mary, 1910; 192197 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Since Maggie Dooley Learned the Hooley Hooley, 1916; 192196 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Since O'Keefe is On Relief, 1935; 192195 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Sing A Good Old Irish Song For Me, 1917; 192194 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Sing An Irish Song To-Night, 1914; 192193 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Sing Me An Irish Come-All-Ye, 1911; 192192 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Sing to Me of Ould Ireland, 1927; 192191 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Singer Was Irish, The, 1914; 192190 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Sister of Rosie O'Grady, The, 1918; 192189 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Skids Are Out To-Day, The, 1879; 192188 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Skin-A-Ma-Rink-A-Rink-A-Ree, 1924; 192187 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Slaunthe!, 1918; 192186 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Smiles and the Tears of Killarney, The, 1917; 192185 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Smiling Irish Eyes, 1929; 192184 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Snowy-Breasted Pearl, The, 1912; 192183 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - So Long, Mister Flanagan, 1910; 192182 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Soldier's Song, The, 1959; 192181 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Solid for Mulhooly, 1881; 192180 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Soliloquy, The, 1903; 192179 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Somewhere in France Dear Mother, 1915; 192178 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Somewhere in Ireland, 1917; 192177 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Songs in Exile, 1908; 192176 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Songs of Shamus O'Brien, 1866; 192175 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Songtime in Erin, 1923; 192174 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Son of an Irishman, The, 1913; 192173 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Song that Reaches Irish Hearts, The, 1911; 192172 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Squaw Colleen, 1910; 192171 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Steerin' for Erin, 1923; 192170 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - St. James Infirmary, 1930; 192169 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Stone Outside Dan Murphy's Door, The, 1895; 192168 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Story the Shamrock Told, The, 1913; 192167 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - St. Patrick's Day, undated; 192166 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - St. Patrick's Day (2), undated; 192165 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - St. Patrick's Day in the USA, 1918; 192164 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - St. Patrick's Day is a Bad Day for Coons, 1901; 192163 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - St. Patrick's Day Waltz, 1856; 192162 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Sullivan, 1908; 192161 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Sunday Night at Nellie's Home, 1894; 192160 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Supposin', 1909; 192159 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Sure Me Heart Is Longin' For You Dear Old Ireland, 1918; 192158 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Sweet Eileen Asthore, 1912; 192157 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Sweet Eileen Machree, 1891; 192156 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Sweet Irish Rose, 1915; 192155 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Sweet Irish Sweetheart of Mine, 1937; 192154 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Sweet Katie Kilcaire, 1874; 192153 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Sweet Katie, the Pride of Tralee, undated; 585048 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Sweet Katie Riley, 1895; 192152 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Sweet Katy Carney, My Lass from Killarney, 1898; 192151 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Sweet Little Irish Girl, 1910; 192150 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Sweet Little Irish Maiden, 1896; 192149 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Sweet Little Kate Maloney, 1900; 192148 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Sweet Little Kate McCoy, 1894; 192147 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Sweet Little Mollie O'Neal, 1897; 192146 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Sweet Little Peggy O'Shea, 1916; 192145 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Sweet Mary Ann, 1878; 192144 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Sweet Molly Malone, 1940; 192143 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Sweet Norah Daly, 1919; 192142 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Sweet Nora Doone, 1907; 192141 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Sweet Nora O'Neale, 1902; 192140 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Sweet Rosie O'Grady, nd, 1896, 1924, 1944; 192139 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Sweet Violets, 1882; 192138 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Sweetest Little Girl in Tipperary, The, 1928; 192137 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Sweetheart Darlin', 1933; 192136 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Sweetheart of O'Callahan's Mills, 1951; 192135 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Sweetheart Song, 1916; 192134 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Swim Out O'Grady, 1894; 192133 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - T, 334234
    - Taffy's Got His Jenny in Glamorgan, 1915; 192132 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Take a Look at Molly, 1923; 192131 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Take Me Back to Erin's Isle Once More, 1915; 192130 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Take Me Back to Ireland to My Little Irish Rose, 1913; 192129 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Take Me Back to My Sweet Shannon Rose, 1918; 192128 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Take Off Your Hats to Old Ireland, 1910; 192127 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Tam O'Shanter, undated; 192126 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Teaching McFadden to Waltz, 1890; 192125 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Tears of an Irish Mother, The, 1921; 192124 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Tears of the Shannon, 1925; 192123 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Teddy O'Neil, 1947; 192122 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Tell It To Sweeny, 1910; 192121 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Tell the Band to Play an Irish Tune, 1906; 192120 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Terence's Farewell to Kathleen, undated; 192119 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Thady O'Flinn, undated; 192118 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - That Little Bit of Green, 1910; 192117 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - That Little Old House of O'Reilly's, 1922; 192116 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - That Old Irish Mother of Mine, 1920, 1925; 192115 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - That Tumble-Down Shack in Athlone, 1918; 192114 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - That's How I Spell I-R-E-L-A-N-D, 1931; 192113 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - That's How the Shannon Flows, 1915; 192112 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - That's How You Can Tell They're Irish, 1920; 192111 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - That's Irish Love, 1912; 192110 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - That's the Irish in Me, 1918; 192109 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - That's the Meaning of I-R-E-L-A-N-D, 1916; 192108 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - That's What Ireland Means to Me, 1917; 192107 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - That's What You Get for Being Irish, 1908; 192106 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - That's Why God Loves the Irish, 1919; 192105 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - There Goes McManus, 1889; 192104 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - There Never Was a Coward Where the Shamrock Grows, 1880; 192103 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - There'll Never Be a League of Nations Without Ireland, 1920; 192102 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - There's A Charm of Dear Old Ireland in Your Eyes, 1918; 192101 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - There's a Dear Spot in Ireland, 1878; 192100 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - There's a Dear Spot in Ireland (2), 1917; 192099 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - There's a Heart in Old Ireland, undated; 192098 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - There's a Little Bit of Irish Everywhere, 1919; 192097 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - There's a Little Bit of Irish in Sadie Cohn, 1916; 192096 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - There's A Little Bit of Irish in Us All, 1938; 192095 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - There's a Mother Back in Ireland Waits for Me, 1914; 192094 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - There's a Rose in Old Erin, 1915; 192093 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - There's a Rose that is Blooming in Ireland, 1917; 192092 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - There's a Typical Tipperary Over Here, 1920; 192091 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - There's a Wee Bit of Blarney in Killarney, 1915; 192090 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - There's Another Angel Now in Old Killarney, 1917; 192089 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Theres No Song Like an Irish Song, 1952; 192088 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - There's Nothing Like the Smile of the Irish, 1941; 192087 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - There's Something in the Name of Ireland, 1917; 192086 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - They Sail'd Away, 1916; 192085 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - They Were Irish, 1906; 192084 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - They've Won Every Nation's Battles But Their Own, 1910; 192083 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Tho' I Had a Bit o' the Devil in Me, She Had the Ways of an Angel, Had She, 1916; 192082 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Tho' I'm a Long Long Way from Tipperary, 1914; 192081 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Those Songs Mother Used to Sing, 1904; 192080 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Three Leaves of Shamrock, 1890; 192079 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Three Leaves of Shamrock (2), 1889; 192078 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Three Lovely Lasses in Bannion, 1940; 192077 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Throw Him Down, McCloskey, 1942; 192076 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Till Ireland's Wrongs Are Righted, 1880; 192075 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Till My Luck Comes Rolling Along, 1922; 192074 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Tim Rooney's at the Fightin'!, 1915; 192073 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Tipperary, 1907; 192072 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Tipperary (2), undated; 192071 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Tipperary Guards, 1915; 192070 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Tipperary March, 1908; 192069 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Tipperary Twirl, The, 1911; 192068 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Tip-Top Tipperary Mary, 1914; 192067 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Tis A Mem'ry of Your Daddy And That Isle Across the Sea, 1915; 192066 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Tis an Irish Girl I Love and She's Just Like You, 1919; 192065 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Tis Only A Sprig of Shamrock, 1915; 192064 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Tis the Last Rose of Summer, undated; 192063 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - To H-L Wid Reform, 1898; 192062 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Told You So, 1945; 192061 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Too-Ra-Loo-Ra-Loo-Ral That's An Irish Lullaby, 1913, 1941, 1944; 192060 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Top o' the Mornin', 1905; 192059 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Top o' the Mornin' (2), 1907; 192058 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Top o' the Mornin', The, 1920; 192057 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Top o' the Morning, The, 1909; 192056 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - To You it's Only Ireland, undated; 192055 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Twas Only an Irishman's Dream, 1916; 192054 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Two Irish Eyes, undated; 192053 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Two Irish Eyes of Tender Blue, 1900; 192052 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Two Laughing Irish Eyes, 1915; 192051 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Two More to Come, 1883; 192050 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - U, 334233
    - Umph-Ah-Ah, 1895; 192049 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Uncle Reilly, 1890; 192048 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Under the Irish Moon, 1909; 192047 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Up Comes McGinty, 1915; 192046 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - V, 334232
    - Vales of Killarney, The, undated; 192045 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Variations on an Irish Melody, 1935; 192044 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Vocal Gems, undated; 192043 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - W, 334231
    - Wait till I lay my hands upon McNally!, 1893; 192042 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - We Americans, 1927; 192041 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - We Couldn't Get Along Without the Irish, 1912; 192040 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Wearers of the Green, 1906; 192039 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Wearing of the Green, 1865; 192038 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Wearing of the Green, The, 1860; 192037 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Wearing of the Green, The (2), 1909; 192036 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Wedding of Barney and Bedalia, The, 1904; 192035 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - We'll Go Back to Erin Someday Mavourneen, 1909; 192034 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Well, the Irish and the Germans Got Together, 1928; 192033 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - What's the Matter with the Irish, 1916; 192032 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - When Chu-Ching-San Weds Paddy McCann, 1920; 192031 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - When Fortune Smiles on You, 1916; 192030 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - When Hogan Paid His Rent, 1933; 192029 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - When I Come Back to Erin, 1916; 192028 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - When I Dream of Killarney and You, 1915; 192027 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - When I Dream of Old Erin, 1912, 1931; 192026 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - When I Found You, 1917; 192025 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - When I Look In Your Eyes, Mavourneen, 1918; 192024 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - When I Met You at the Fair in Tipperary, 1912; 192023 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - When I Rode on the Choo Choo Cars, 1905; 192022 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - When Ireland Comes Into Her Own, 1919; 192021 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - When Ireland Takes Her Place Among the Nations of the Earth, 1919; 192020 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - When Irish Eyes Are Smiling, 1912; 192019 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - When Irish Toes Are Waltzing, 1943; 192018 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - When It's Moonlight in Mayo, 1913; 192017 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - When It's Moonlight in Mayo (2), 1954; 192016 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - When It's Springtime in Killarney, 1915, 1916; 192015 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - When John McCormack Sings A Song, 1915; 192014 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - When Johnny Comes Marching Home, 1863; 192013 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - When June Comes Along With A Song, 1923; 192012 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - When Kelly Sang Killarney, 1917; 192011 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - When My Girl From Tipp'rary Tips Me, 1907; 192010 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - When Old Ireland Is Forgotten, 1914; 192009 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - When Reuben Comes to Town, 1900; 334229 (Box 41, Folder 3A)
    - When Rubenstein and Mendelssohn Played the Wearing of the Green, 1912; 192008 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - When Scanlan Sang Mavourneen, 1917; 192007 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - When the Angelus is Ringing in Ireland, 1923; 192006 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - When the Bloom is on the Clover, Molly Dear, 1907; 192005 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - When the Dew is on the Clover in Kildare, 1909; 192004 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - When the Fightin' Irish Come Home, 1919; 192003 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - When the Gates of Heaven Opened, 1917; 192002 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - When the Moon Shines in Ireland, 1914, 1917; 192001 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - When the Rose of Tralee Met Danny Boy, 1940; 192000 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - When the Sun Sets in Galway, 1915; 191999 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - When the Sun Sets in Ireland, 1917; 191998 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - When the Sunbeams are Kissing the Roses, 1919; 191997 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - When They Planted the Shamrock, 1928; 191996 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - When They Play the River Shannon, 1916; 191995 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - When They Sing the Wearin' of the Green, 1929; 191994 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - When You and I Were Young, Maggie, nd, 1866, 1935; 191993 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - When You Break an Irishman's Heart, 1949; 191992 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - When You Come Back, 1928; 565209 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - When You Talk about Old Ireland, 1950; 191991 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Where Be Going?, 1898; 191990 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Where Irish Skies Are Smiling, 1918; 191989 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Where Is Mavourneen Tonight?, 1904; 191988 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Where the Golden Rod is Waving, Mollie Dear, 1906; 191987 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Where the River Liffy Flows, 1916; 191986 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Where the River Shannon Flows, 1905; 191985 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Where the Shamrock Grows, 1916; 191984 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Where the Shandon Bells Are Ringing, 1914; 191983 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Where the Shannon Flows Down to the Sea, 1938; 191982 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Where the Silvery Sleney's Flowing, 1912; 191981 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Where the Sparrows and Chippies Parade, 1888; 191980 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Where's Kitty O'Brien?, 1910; 191979 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - While the Irish Moon Rolls On, 1932; 191978 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Who Ever Heard of and Irishman Singing the Blues?, 1952; 191977 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Who Said the Irish Don't Love Liberty?, 1919; 191976 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Who Threw the Overalls in Mistress Murphy's Chowder?, 1932; 191975 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Why Did They Sell Killarney?, 1899; 191974 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Why Don't They Dance the Good Old Dances of Ireland, 1912; 191973 (Box 42, Folder 11)